const STORE = [
  {
      question: 'When was Everton FC founded?',
      answers: [
        '1888',
        '1878',
        '1900',
        '1902',
        ],
        correctAnswer: '1878',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who are the arch-rivals of Everton FC?',
      answers: [
        'Arsenal FC',
        'Manchester United FC',
        'Crystal Palace FC',
        'Liverpool FC',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Liverpool FC',
    },
    {
      question: 'Where does Everton FC play their home games?',
      answers: [
        'Finch Farm',
        'Anfield Park',
        'Goodison Park',
        'Bellefield',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Goodison Park',
    },
    {
      question: 'How many English League Titles does Everton hold?',
      answers: [
        '9',
        '6',
        '4',
        '0',
        ],
      correctAnswer: '9',
    },
    {
      question: 'What company has their name on the Everton FC jersey in the 2017-2018 season?',
      answers: [
        'Chang Beer',
        'NEC',
        'One2one',
        'SportPesa',
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'SportPesa',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is the current manager of Everton FC?',
      answers: [
        'David Moyes',
        'Harry Catterick',
        'Sam Allardyce',
        'Howard Kendall',
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Sam Allardyce',
    },
    {
      question: 'How many seasons has Everton FC played in Englandâ€™s top tier (Division One/Premier League)?',
      answers: [
      '100',
      '88',
      '105',
      '114',
      ],
      correctAnswer: '114',
    },
    {
      question: 'What Everton FC player has appeared most for the club?',
      answers: [
        'Tim Howard',
        'Dave Watson',
        'Leighton Baines',
        'Neville Southall',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Neville Southall',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is Everton FC\'s all-time leading scorer?',
      answers: [
      'Roy Vernon',
      'Graeme Sharp',
      'Dixie Dean',
      'Bob Latchford',
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Dixie Dean',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the defining feature of the Everton FC team crest?',
      answers: [
        'Prince Rupert\'s Tower',
        'The Liver bird',
        'A cannon',
        'A moose',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Prince Rupert\'s Tower',
    },
];




